<TweetText>RT @EgyTweets RT @CandiCunningham: There are more pyramids in Peru than in Egypt #coolfacts</TweetText><TweetText>RT @OptaJoe: 72% - Man Utd have won 72% of Premier League games with Wayne Rooney starting since Aug 2009 and just 47% without him. Hole.</TweetText><TweetText>RT @IMDb: Here's a clip of Francis Ford Coppola accepting the Irving Thalberg Award at the 2010 Governors Awards. http://imdb.to/dqpMXP</TweetText><TweetText>RT @IMDb: Gus Van Sant and Kelsey Grammer are teaming up for 'Boss', an eight-episode drama series for Starz. http://imdb.to/bqK23n</TweetText><TweetText>RT @markmackinnon: Russia and five other countries won't attend Nobel Peace Prize ceremony for Liu Xiaobo. Barry Manilow and Jamiroquai  ...</TweetText><TweetText>Military notes: Airman Jia Shen graduated from basic training at Lackland Air Force Base, San Antonio. http://bit.ly/cYsnmw</TweetText><TweetText>RT @THR: Daniel Day-Lewis to Play Abraham Lincoln in Steven Spielberg Directed Biopic http://bit.ly/aonM7U</TweetText><TweetText>RT @TMZ: Paris Hilton continued paying off her debt to society by cleaning graffiti on the streets of Hollywood -- and wo... http://bit. ...</TweetText><TweetText>Rigoberta Menchu winner of the Nobel Peace Prize Guatemala http://t.co/wXj9nCQ via @youtube</TweetText><TweetText>RT @IMDb: As expected, 'Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows' leads the Friday #boxoffice, taking in an est. $61.2 million. http://imdb. ...</TweetText><TweetText>RT @FIFA_Newz: Twente fail to keep PSV pace - FC Twente slipped up in their attempts to keep pace with Eredivisie leaders PSV Eindh... h ...</TweetText><TweetText>BBC: Anne Hathaway to co-host Nobel peace prize concert http://is.gd/hvd61</TweetText><TweetText>RT @ESPNsoccernet: Benitez urges united front ahead of Twente clash: Inter Milan boss Rafael Benitez has urged everyone at Inter Mi... h ...</TweetText><TweetText>RT @OptaJoe: 25 - The move for Yaya Touré's goal against Fulham involved 25 passes; the most for any goal in the Premier League this sea ...</TweetText><TweetText>The famous 1984 Macintosh ad was directed by Ridley Scott, director of Alien and Gladiator.</TweetText><TweetText>RT @ebertchicago: Klaus Kinski died in 1991, or so we are assured. http://j.mp/b5pPRr</TweetText><TweetText>RT @IMDb: Johnny Depp will star as Tonto in 'The Lone Ranger,' re-teaming with Gore Verbinski and Jerry Bruckheimer. http://imdb.to/fDyVGO</TweetText><TweetText>RT @FIFAWorldCupTM: Hyundai - Kia drives on as FIFA Partner until 2022 - FIFA is pleased to announce the extension of the partnership with .</TweetText><TweetText>I just met the owner of my company Harold Simmons in the elevator. The richest man in Dallas. He's on wikipedia: http://bit.ly/fiWX7M</TweetText><TweetText>RT @jimenaofficial: FoxSports Rangers vs Man U . Fox Sports+ Milan vs Twente . FoxSports HD Panathinaikos vs Barcelona . Links de partid ...</TweetText><TweetText>RT @OptaJoe: 12 - Peter Crouch has scored 12 Champions League goals in 29 appearances, compared to 60 in 239 in the Premier League. Nachos.</TweetText><TweetText>RT @OMGFacts: Detroit is located NORTH of Canada! Details --&gt; http://bit.ly/cDxGFW</TweetText><TweetText>Florence: The Cultural Capital of Europe http://t.co/XgpDBC9 via @sfgate</TweetText><TweetText>RT @ISRAEL21C: Director Bergman wins second Tokyo Film Festival prize http://su.pr/1usSq8 #Israel #film</TweetText><TweetText>Sad news... RIP Peter Christopherson, directed videos for RATM, NIN, Ministry, and many others. http://bit.ly/bia801 CC: @tmorello</TweetText><TweetText>RT @LAhistory: Nov 25, 1920: Auto racer Gaston Chevrolet (bro to Chevrolet founder) died in race @ Beverly Hills Speedway. @Wired: http: ...</TweetText><TweetText>RT @nytimesarts: Arts, Briefly: Ana Maria Matute Wins Cervantes Prize http://nyti.ms/e5Qieg</TweetText><TweetText>Richard Branson scoops German media prize - Yahoo! News http://yhoo.it/hZ1wf6</TweetText><TweetText>I am watching SHINE A LIGHT, the Rolling Stones concert doc directed by Martin Scorsese on VH1 Classics.  Bill (cont) http://tl.gd/765t4b</TweetText><TweetText>RT @TPO_Hisself: I was wrong, I admit it... Obama is the smartest democrat in America, and CLEARLY deserves the Nobel Prize!!!    http:/ ...</TweetText><TweetText>RT @BreakingNews: Veteran comic actor Leslie Nielsen, 84, has died in Ft. Lauderdale, Fla. - CJOB radio http://bit.ly/h9yDyA</TweetText><TweetText>India's exports of gems &amp; jewellery up by 41.6% from April to Oct. to US$ 21.4 billion vs. US$ 15.1 billion in same period last year</TweetText><TweetText>RT @ShowbizSpy: Ben Affleck Could Have Directed Superman http://bit.ly/dX3yMG</TweetText><TweetText>RT @Working_Wood: Barzotti still working – and growing – after 47 years: The owner of Barzotti Woodworking, a major Canadian maker... ht ...</TweetText><TweetText>RT @Yesterday_Today: 2001: Music - the "quiet Beatle," George Harrison, died in Los Angeles, Ca, after a long battle with cancer at age  ...</TweetText><TweetText>RT @espn: Alabama PA announcer fired for songs directed at Auburn's Cam Newton - http://es.pn/dUvP8X</TweetText><TweetText>In 1900, Irish writer Oscar Wilde died in Paris at age 46.</TweetText><TweetText>RT @history_travel: Beirut Lebanon: Beirut is the capital of Lebanon and is the largest city of the country. The city is located on ...  ...</TweetText><TweetText>RT @BBCWorld: David Beckham says he ´trusts´ Fifa will treat England 2018 fairly despite allegations in UK media</TweetText><TweetText>RT @TheAtlantic: By blocking Liu Xiaobo's family from collecting his Nobel Prize, China raises its value: http://ow.ly/3i5xi</TweetText><TweetText>RT @WirelessFest: Congrats to Greg Snelgrove who is the winner of our 'Festival Survey' prize draw! Keep your eyes peeled for more compe ...</TweetText><TweetText>RT @IMDb: Catherine Hardwicke is in talks to direct 'Maze Runners', a film adaptation of James Dashner's sci-fi trilogy. http://imdb.to/ ...</TweetText><TweetText>Wesley Snipes must report to prison authorities in Pennsylvania by 9 December  http://imdb.to/euQjSO</TweetText><TweetText>RT @ebertchicago: Richard Pryor died in 2005. "Next I'm doing Hamlet." http://j.mp/hDKIpi</TweetText><TweetText>RT @HotelChatter: Gansevoort Park opens a Lacoste store today, an Italian restaurant this weekend: http://bit.ly/fkODRL</TweetText><TweetText>RT @HLNTV: Just In: Russia will host the 2018 FIFA #WorldCup. #HLN</TweetText><TweetText>Alan J. Pakula directed Jane Fonda and Donald Sutherland in Klute (1971).  http://is.gd/i6f4i</TweetText><TweetText>RT @euronews: Qatar to host FIFA World Cup in 2022 #fifa #worldcup</TweetText><TweetText>RT @qikipedia: The Salt Palace Hotel in Bolivia is built entirely of salt</TweetText><TweetText>RT @FIFAcom: FIFA.com takes a closer look at TP Mazembe Englebert and their ambitions for the FIFA Club World Cup in December - http://d ...</TweetText><TweetText>RT @legallawwatch: Viacom tries to revive lawsuit to get damages from YouTube: Viacom Inc., the owner of MTV, Comedy Central and Ni... h ...</TweetText><TweetText>BBC: US poet wins Dylan Thomas prize http://is.gd/ibWvK</TweetText><TweetText>RT @InfostradaLive: Pedro gives Barça 1-0 lead vs Osauna. Last 7 Barça league goals are now scored by Spanish players; first time since  ...</TweetText><TweetText>RT @ESPNsoccernet: Liverpool's Fernando Torres claims prize: Liverpool's Fernando Torres has been rewarded for his goalscoring perf... h ...</TweetText><TweetText>RT @ebertchicago: Frank Zappa died in 1993. "Into the, into the RE-productive orifice of a lady harpist, and you were a dwarf, would you ...</TweetText><TweetText>In 1791, composer Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart died in Vienna, Austria, at age 35.</TweetText><TweetText>RT @EgyTweets: RT @Zeinobia: Why Is The U.S Afraid Of Mubarak’s Regime !!? #Egypt #media #citizenJournalism ? http://bit.ly/eLYqcY</TweetText><TweetText>RT @EgyTweets: RT @Zeinobia: ElBaradei Harassed At The Cairo International Airport #Egypt #citizenJournalism #politics ? http://bit.ly/f ...</TweetText><TweetText>FC Twente v Tottenham preview http://bit.ly/hB5hnR</TweetText><TweetText>RT @whereartyou_uk: Susan Philipsz won the Turner Prize - http://tiny.cc/mrvt5 If you are in London, see her work for free - http://tiny ...</TweetText><TweetText>RT @EgyTweets: RT @ProfCasperelli: March 26: Bafana v Egypt at FNB Stadium. March 27: Kings of Leon at FNB Stadium. I foresee problems.</TweetText><TweetText>RT @palestine: Israel allows Gaza to add flowers to farm exports - Reuters http://bit.ly/hUCiOf</TweetText><TweetText>China to award Confucius Peace Prize http://dlvr.it/9zJpt</TweetText><TweetText>Julian Assange should be awarded Nobel peace prize, suggests Russia http://t.co/r9Evpa3 vía @guardian</TweetText><TweetText>RT @washingtonpost: Liu Xiaobo will be the first #Nobel Peace Prize recipient to not attend the award ceremony since 1935. http://wapo.s ...</TweetText><TweetText>RT @EgyTweets: RT @TarikSalama: Mubarak may criticize Qatar, and perhaps Syria, as Iranian surrogates. #cablegate #Egypt #politics  http ...</TweetText><TweetText>RT @EgyTweets: RT @MissWann: The most beautiful women in egypt, she's a legend too. She's Nefertiti</TweetText><TweetText>Javier Bardem played Anton Chigurh in "No Country for Old Men" directed by Joe &amp; Ethan Coen. http://is.gd/iKfgK</TweetText><TweetText>@DulceMaria &gt; Sweet Dawn is a foundation created and directed by actress and singer Dulce Maria  : http://www.dulceamanecer.com.mx/</TweetText><TweetText>RT @new_Parishotels: In Paris? Visit The Tower Montparnasse and experience the panoramic view of the city http://bit.ly/a9urQh #hotel #t ...</TweetText><TweetText>RT @new_Parishotels: Stay at Hotel du Lys and visit The Luxembourg Gardens http://bit.ly/bPAEJX #hotel #travel #Paris #deals</TweetText><TweetText>RT @headlinenews: CNN: Violence flares in Ivory Coast: Explosions and gunfire were heard Thursday in the capital of the Ivory Coas... ht ...</TweetText><TweetText>RT @LarryTaunton: The Battle of Verdun ended on this day in 1916. I've been there. Haunting. 1.5 million casualties. Homo homini lupus:  ...</TweetText><TweetText>Obama should be stripped of his Nobel Peace Prize for drones, get Nobel War Crime Prize. Julian Assange for Nobel Peace Prize.</TweetText><TweetText>London Named Tuberculosis Capital Of Western Europe - Health News - redOrbit http://t.co/cVWQya4 #health #disease</TweetText><TweetText>Ancient Thai capital of #Ayutthaya, #Thailand. http://yfrog.com/h2cppnj</TweetText><TweetText>Xo Paris Hilton Pictures - Paris Hilton Presents Supermatxe Motorbikes in Madrid - Zimbio http://goo.gl/aRMlT</TweetText><TweetText>#DarkAngel was directed by James Cameron - who would've thought...</TweetText><TweetText>Leonardo Di Caprio would have never acted in unstoppable</TweetText><TweetText>RT @LifelineLive: Paris Hilton launches new motorcycle racing team http://usat.ly/e0YHaB</TweetText><TweetText>RT @mashable: Johnny Depp and “Inception” Top IMDb User Picks for 2010 - http://on.mash.to/dSLuK6</TweetText><TweetText>RT @ebertchicago: John Steinbeck died in 1968. "Wherever there's a fight, so hungry people can eat, I'll be there." http://bit.ly/fHlUpv</TweetText><TweetText>To/@ParisHilton TRUe :Paris Hilton Is Pregnant? | The Stir http://goo.gl/8oyKl</TweetText><TweetText>RT @TMZ: Paris Hilton and other passengers on a Delta flight from Los Angeles to Maui were taken off the plane at LAX, af... http://bit. ...</TweetText><TweetText>RT @peoplemag: Paris Hilton's flight to Hawaii evacuated after knife found on board: http://ow.ly/3sNFJ</TweetText><TweetText>RT @JohnHamptonK: No Tells: Best Poetry Books of 2010 - Lucy Biederman: Lucy Biederman graduated from George Mason University's MF... ht ...</TweetText><TweetText>RT @derekrootboy: Has David Cameron not acted illegally by handing Jeremy Hunt decision on BSkyB? They're both in Rupert Murdoch's pocke ...</TweetText><TweetText>FACT: When table tennis was originally created in 1889, it was called gossima.</TweetText><TweetText>BBC: Lebanese film Stray Bullet wins Dubai film prize http://is.gd/jdHIm</TweetText><TweetText>Walter Scott (1771–1832): Richard Thorpe directed Robert Taylor, Elizabeth Taylor and Joan Fontaine in "Ivanhoe" (1952)  http://is.gd/jehHo</TweetText><TweetText>RT @ebertchicago: Today Nathanael West (Day of the Locust, Miss Lonelyhearts) died in a crash while driving to Scott Fitzgerald's funera ...</TweetText><TweetText>BBC: Graffiti artist Banksy up for London critics film prize http://is.gd/jfDdQ  http://yfrog.com/h4x14ij</TweetText><TweetText>@Yoda_Bot Frank Oz Born in Hereford, England, born Frank Oznowicz graduated from California's Oakland City College, Muppets, Yoda #Sithmas</TweetText><TweetText>RT @sbtrib: South Bend Tribune: First black woman said to have graduated from Notre Dame dies http://bit.ly/h15d7N</TweetText><TweetText>RT @Arsenal_Chris: Marouane Chamakh believes he can establish himself as one of the best strikers in the Premier League.</TweetText><TweetText>RT @wsjindia: India Tightens Rules on Cotton Exports http://on.wsj.com/eV2UD9</TweetText><TweetText>FACT: Dr. William Moulton Marston, the man who created Wonder Woman, also designed an early lie detector.</TweetText><TweetText>FIFA 11 on xbox 360 nice 1 bro!. :D</TweetText><TweetText>RT @OMGFacts: 300 million years ago, the United Kingdom was located at the Equator. It's climate was like Central Africa is now.</TweetText><TweetText>RT @cnnbrk: Tour bus in which 8 U.S. #tourists died in Aswan, #Egypt, crashed into parked dump truck loaded with sand. http://on.cnn.com ...</TweetText><TweetText>Dimitar Berbatov scored twice as Manchester United eased past Sunderland to stay firmly in control of the Premier League title race.</TweetText><TweetText>In 1972, the 33rd president of the United States, Harry S. Truman, died in Kansas City, Mo., at age 88.</TweetText><TweetText>In 2006, former President Gerald R. Ford died in Rancho Mirage, Calif., at age 93.</TweetText><TweetText>Luchino Visconti directed Marcello Mastroianni, Anna Karina and Bernard Blier in "The Stranger" (1967) http://is.gd/jvtUQ</TweetText><TweetText>Manchester United maintained their Premier League leadership with a routine 2-0 win against Sunderland at Old Trafford.</TweetText><TweetText>Michael Caton-Jones directed Liam Neeson, Jessica Lange and John Hurt in "Rob Roy" (1995)  http://is.gd/jvJ0w</TweetText><TweetText>RT @rolandsmartin: Mike Gardner, the manager of @teenamarie, just told me that it is true: the legendary R&amp;B singer has indeed died.</TweetText><TweetText>RT @AJEnglish: Snakes creeping out Bangkok: As the capital of Thailand continues growing, it is encroaching on the habitat of t... http: ...</TweetText><TweetText>RT @IMDb: Congratulations are in order for Natalie Portman, who's engaged to choreographer Benjamin Millepied, and pregnant too http://i ...</TweetText><TweetText>RT @HackneyAbbott: David Milliband becomes "Our Man in Washington" Consolation prize for losing Labour leadership. http://t.co/CEJmA2k</TweetText><TweetText>RT @AS_carrusel: PREMIER LEAGUE.  Gol: Manchester C. 2 (Lescott min. 13) - Aston Villa 0</TweetText><TweetText>WP Opinion: Mohamed ElBaradei • Egypt's real state of emergency is its repressed democracy http://is.gd/jFYCk</TweetText><TweetText>RT @ebertchicago: Sam Peckinpah died in 1984. I was at the Bahamas junket when "The Wild Bunch" stirred froths of rage. http://bit.ly/9KSZ1S</TweetText><TweetText>RT @USDOL: DOL awards nearly $20 million to combat exploitive child labor in Bolivia, Egypt and Jordan [12/29/2010] http://bit.ly/hIVGai</TweetText><TweetText>RT @museummedia: RT @PostalMuseum Wonderful video, "History of U.S. Postage," created by design student Catheryn Davenel: http://ht.ly/3vPBT</TweetText><TweetText>Gillian Armstrong directed "Love, Lust &amp; Lies" (2009)  http://is.gd/jJ7R5</TweetText><TweetText>RT @CraftGossip: Top 10 Projects from 2010: Shellie, the owner of Craft Gossip, was kind enough to let me start the Home &amp; Garden... htt ...</TweetText><TweetText>RT @washingtonpost: Notable figures who died in 2010: J.D. Salinger, Gary Coleman, Dorothy Height, Rue McClanahan, many others. PHOTOS:  ...</TweetText><TweetText>RT @governpoint: William Greider's critique of the traditional media's Social Security failure: Via digby, Nyhan Prize winner and... htt ...</TweetText><TweetText>RT @BreakingNews: Explosion reported at a Coptic church in Alexandria, Egypt; several killed - BBC.com http://bbc.in/exGCJo</TweetText><TweetText>Watching "Collateral" (2004) with Tom Cruise Jamie Farr.  Never saw it except bits and pieces.  Good Hyper-Action ---  http://imdb.to/hFK4uy</TweetText><TweetText>Istanbul thrives as the new party capital of Europe http://t.co/I2M3d69 via @guardian</TweetText><TweetText>RT @ReutersMoney: Iran says no gap in oil exports to India http://in.reuters.com/article/idINIndia-53879120110102</TweetText><TweetText>Kenneth Branagh directed Robert De Niro, himself and Helena Bonham Carter in "Frankenstein" (1994). http://is.gd/jYBun</TweetText><TweetText>RT @Mrityunjoykjha: King George 5 of Eng announced, in 1911, the transfer of the capital of British India from Calcutta to Delhi. ...</TweetText><TweetText>RT @artinfodotcom: The late Malcom McLaren on his film "Paris, Capital of the 21st Century" and why the old guys are the most radical: h ...</TweetText><TweetText>RT @IMDb: More sad news... Actress Annie Francis, best known for 'Forbidden Planet', died Sunday at age 80. http://imdb.to/gJHRyX #resti ...</TweetText><TweetText>When I used to hear Donnell Jones "Where I'll Go" it was time to turn off my TAPE before it played Lucy Pearl"s Dance 2nite video!!</TweetText><TweetText>Texas A &amp; M d. Abilene Christian, 5-3 in exhibition. Other than dubs for ACU, Jake Hendrie d Calon Alpar 76 76 in all-centex match</TweetText><TweetText>Notre Dame vs Marquette Live NCAA Basketball Stream Online TV Link ...: Watch basketball match live online on yo... http://bit.ly/gxvDL3</TweetText><TweetText>Australia Vs England live free 3rd One Day International Cricket match... http://ff.im/wGZDo</TweetText><TweetText>#tennis Amazing match between Schiavone vs Kuznetsova. Epic match!</TweetText><TweetText>Schiavone beats Kuznetsova 16-14 in the third.... the prize.... a match against the Kangaroo fighter herself Caroline Wozniacki</TweetText><TweetText>6 - Udinese have scored two or more goals in each of their last six league fixtures, including today's match against Inter. Good form</TweetText><TweetText>Manchester United manager Sir Alex Ferguson pushes Wayne Rooney to match ... - Goal.com http://bit.ly/fe4vrg</TweetText><TweetText>Francesca Schiavone made history today as she was part of the longest women's match in Grand Slam history,... http://tinyurl.com/45679qn</TweetText><TweetText>Blackburn 1-0 West Brom at the break - half time match report here: http://bit.ly/igWFDk</TweetText><TweetText>Jacqueline Obradors - IMDb: Jacqueline Obradors, Actress: Six Days Seven Nights. Born in the San Fernando ... http://tinyurl.com/4qhagdq</TweetText><TweetText>And the recap in English: Handball World Championships - Denmark beat Argentina 31-24 and are ready for the semis with one group match left!</TweetText><TweetText>Half time: Sampdoria 0-0 Juventus..... Dry match......... *yawns*</TweetText><TweetText>Mark Schwarzer is one match away from equalling Alex Tobin's 87 #Socceroos caps record! #ac2011</TweetText><TweetText>Schiavone wins marathon match at Australian Open: Rob Griffith / AP Italy's Francesca Schiavone celebrates a poi... http://bit.ly/eg0vQZ</TweetText><TweetText>Glee Stars Party In Las Vegas For Rivera's Birthday:  http://imdb.to/i8Zbp6 [IMDb movie news]</TweetText><TweetText>Sky News understands that Richard Keys and Andy Gray are to be stood down from covering Chelsea - Bolton match tonight.</TweetText><TweetText>Keith Olbermann has left MSNBC, effective immediately. http://imdb.to/eDAQTv</TweetText><TweetText>Explosion has killed 20 and injured 35 near the Shia city of Kerbala in Iraq</TweetText><TweetText>Real Madrid - Sevilla Copa history. The Whites have won seven of eleven matches and the two most recent semifinal ties</TweetText><TweetText>Sydney FC accepts Reddy ban - Liam Reddy will miss Sydney FC's next two A-League matches after the club accepted his... http://ow.ly/1b0ZrY</TweetText><TweetText>Hosni Albarek :) RT @ouchem : Hosni Mubarak Assumed office 29 years and 103 days ago @25Egypt #25jan #Egypt</TweetText><TweetText>Why not do this, Mr. President? End the wars in Iraq and Afghanistan.</TweetText><TweetText>Naomi Watts joins the cast of Clint Eastwood's 'J. Edgar', w/ Leonardo DiCaprio, Armie Hammer &amp; Ed Westwick. http://imdb.to/glh13F</TweetText><TweetText>Closed-captioning "A Night in the Life of Jimmy Reardon" (1988) with River Phoenix http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0095736/</TweetText><TweetText>FUN FACT! "Belgium is on course to beat Iraq’s 289 days without a government."</TweetText><TweetText>Check out IMDb's video interview with Sir Anthony Hopkins, as he discusses his latest film, 'The Rite'. http://imdb.to/e4PnLB</TweetText><TweetText>@mmflint And if they're worried about Egypt becoming unstable over Mubarak getting the boot, then what justification was there for Iraq?</TweetText><TweetText>Steve Buscemi just won the first SAG Award of the night for Boardwalk Empire. We're updating the winners live! http://imdb.to/gPpKZ6</TweetText><TweetText>RT @amaramacleod: The International community must demand that #Mubarak steps down. He must negotiate the transition with #ElBaradie</TweetText><TweetText>Extreme Makeover: Home Edition (TV Series 2003– ) - IMDb: With Ty Pennington, Paul DiMeo, Michael Moloney, Tracy... http://bit.ly/gMfCK5</TweetText><TweetText>Happy Birthday Michael C. Hall! http://imdb.to/gbM5Bm #borntoday #dexter</TweetText><TweetText>RT @IMDb Joseph Gordon-Levitt is joining Christopher Nolan's The Dark Knight rises; he may be The Riddler. http://imdb.to/gNaSRG</TweetText><TweetText>Joseph Gordon-Levitt is joining Christopher Nolan's The Dark Knight rises; rumor has it he may be The Riddler. http://imdb.to/gNaSRG</TweetText><TweetText>I'm watching Match of the Day! Man City's defending at times reminded me of Arsenal's defending! Shocking! #Fail</TweetText>